Matthew Lluis Web Developer

linkedin.com/in/mwlluis github.com/MattTheMicrowave matthewlluis.com

About Me...

I am an Austin-based, full-stack Web Developer. I am experienced with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, along with the Bootstrap, Angular.js, Express.js, and Backbone.js frameworks, in addition to the Node.js platform. I like to build, I like to share, and I really (really) like to learn.

Experience

February 2016 – present

khmertuktuk.com, khmertuktuk.com/spanish.html Webmaster/Web Developer

This is a website that I created and maintain for my friend's tuk-tuk service in Siem Reap, Cambodia. It was built from scratch in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I also built a Spanishlanguage version.

August 2015 – present

eyehategod.ee, facebook.com/OfficialEyehateGod Web Developer/Contributor/Administrator

These are the official websites of the New Orleans-based band, I maintain, design, and edit the client-side components of eyehategod.ee, coding in HTML, CSS, and Javascript languages.

May 2013 – present

the kings of metal. com/blog

Writer/Administrator

This is a travel blog site, built with WordPress, that I write for and maintain using the WordPress platform to edit and modify the layout and functionality of the content.

Skills

Portfolio: matthewlluis.com/portfolio.html

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery,

PHP, Python

Frameworks: Bootstrap, Angular.js, Backbone.js, Express.js, Mongoose.js

Databases: MongoDB

Platforms: Node.js, Amazon Web Services

Software: Atom (text editor), Brackets (text editor), Git (command line), WordPress, Adobe

Creative Suite, Microsoft Office Suite

Additional Languages: Fluency in Spanish

(Conversing, Reading, Writing)

Education

Austin Coding Academy, Austin, TX Completed Full-Stack Advanced Track, 2016

Speakeasy Language School, Barcelona, Spain Completed Intensive Spanish Program, 2014

The University of Texas at Austin, Austin, TX PhD in Biochemistry, 2009

University of South Florida, Tampa, FL B.S. in Chemistry, 2004

Contact



(512) 806-9176



matthew.w.lluis@gmail.com